Terrence Luciano

Oak Ridge, NJ 07438 973-440-7137 terryluciano1@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://www.terrenceluciano.com GitHub: https://github.com/TerryLDev

Summary

Full-Stack Developer with 3+ years of programming experience in backend and frontend web development. Strong skills in programming, project management, and CAD Modeling. Ability to handle challenges, learn new skills quickly, and swiftly adapt to project changes. Able to work with a team or alone in a remote or on-site work environment.

Education

August 2018 - May 2021

County College of Morris, Randolph, NJ - Associates Degree in Information Technology

March 2023 - (Expected) May 2024

William Paterson University, College of Science and Health, Wayne, NJ – Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Skills

• Frontend: Vue.js, React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

• Backend: Python, Node.js, Express.js, Bash Script, C/C++

Databases: MongoDB, MySQL

• Other: Figma, Heroku, Git, Fusion 360, Onshape

Experience

June 2022 - November 2022

Rutgers Data Science Consulting, Newark, NJ - Computer Science Project Lead

- Worked with Johnson & Johnson Innovation to develop an automated system for generating personalized PDF Reports for business innovators. (Python, HTML, CSS)
- Converted business innovators' survey results into an easy-to-read PDF report.
- Designed report mockups using Figma with multiple design iterations.
- Help push report generation system into a production environment.

May 2019 - August 2020

Best Buy, Riverdale, NJ - Sales Associate

- Crafted unique technology solutions to meet a customer's needs.
- Provided friendly and helpful customer service.
- Made computer and other technology sales.
- Kept up to date with the latest technology.